A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices xFA116
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Field Offices - Paris, 1935-1976, undated; 1; 54.8 Cubic Feet 149 document cases
  - Postwar, 1945-1959; 2; 81 Boxes; 42 cubic feet
    - Postwar - Correspondence, 2.01
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Human Anatomy - Reprints (12), 1947-1955 (Box 24, Folder 222)
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Institute of Physiology, 1929-1935, 1949-1957 (Box 25, Folder 223)
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Laboratory of Human Nutrition, 1947-1957 (Box 25, Folder 224)
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Infirmary, 1941-1954 (Box 25, Folder 225)
        (centrifuge) - 1941-1947 (Coombs, Patricia) - 1941-1954
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Infirmary, 1941-1954 (Box 25, Folder 226)
      - DMPH England - Oxford University - Radcliffe Medical School, 1954-1957 (Box 25, Folder 227)
      - DMPH England - Rickham, Peter Paul - (travel, pediatric surgery), 1950-1952 (Box 25, Folder 228)
      - DMPH England - Pemberton, John - (travel, social medicine), 1950-1954 (Box 25, Folder 229)
      - DMPH England - Roffey Park Rehabilitation Center, 1947-1953 (Box 25, Folder 230)
      - DMPH England - Roth, Martin - (neuropsychiatry), 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 231)
      - DMPH England - Royal Anthropological Institute - Blood Group, 1951-1955 (Box 25, Folder 232)
      - DMPH England - Royal College of Nursing, 1946-1953 (Box 25, Folder 233)
      - DMPH England - Royal National Throat, Nose, and Ear Hospital, 1948-1954 (Box 25, Folder 234)
      - DMPH England - Royal Sanitary Institute, 1951-1954 (Box 25, Folder 235)
        Margate Congress - 1951-1952 Hastings Congress - 1952-1953 Scarborough Congress - 1953-1954
      - DMPH England - Royal Society of Medicine, 1949-1954 (Box 25, Folder 236)
      - DMPH England - Royal Victoria Infirmary - Child Health Department, 1947-1955 (Box 25, Folder 237)
      - DMPH England - Royal Victoria Infirmary and King's College Medical School - Department of Psychological Medicine, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 238)
      - DMPH England - St. Bartholemew's Hospital - Department of Pathology, 1953-1956 (Box 26, Folder 239)
      - DMPH England - St. George's Hospital School of Nursing, 1953-1955 (Box 26, Folder 240)
      - DMPH England - St. Mary's Hospital Medical School, 1943-1944, 1952-1955 (Box 26, Folder 241)
      - DMPH England - St. Thomas Hospital - Medical School, 1947-1953 (Box 26, Folder 242)
      - DMPH England - St. Thomas Hospital - Sherrington School of Physiology, 1949-1955 (Box 26, Folder 243)
      - DMPH England - St. Thomas Hospital - Sherrington School of Physiology, 1949-1955 (Box 26, Folder 244)
      - DMPH England - Sanitary Engineering, 1949-1954 (Box 26, Folder 245)
      - DMPH England - Sanitary Engineers Association, 1950-1955 (Box 26, Folder 246)
      - DMPH England, 1948-1955 (Box 26, Folder 247)
        Schlesinger, Bernard - (pediatrics) - 1952-1954 Scholl, Donald Arthur - (travel, anatomy) - 1952 Sinclair, David - (travel, human anatomy) - 1948-1955 Smith, J.H.F. - (travel, industrial hygiene) - 1953-1954
      - DMPH England, 1947-1958 (Box 26, Folder 248)
        Social Medicine Research Unit - 1947-1958 Documents (6) - 1948-1950
      - DMPH England, 1952-1954 (Box 26, Folder 249)
        Thompson, Donald R. - (fellowship, tuberculosis) - 1952-1954 Truelove, Sidney C. - (travel, clinical medicine) - 1952-1954
      - DMPH England - University College, London, 1948-1955 (Box 27, Folder 250)
      - DMPH England - University College, London - Department of Anatomy, 1951-1958 (Box 27, Folder 251)
      - DMPH England - University College, London - Department of Anthropology, 1954-1958 (Box 27, Folder 252)
      - DMPH England - University College, London - Department of Civil and Municipal Engineering, 1950-1956 (Box 27, Folder 253)
      - DMPH England - University of London, 1954-1955 (Box 27, Folder 254)
      - DMPH England, 1950-1954 (Box 27, Folder 255)
        Williams, H.C. Maurice - (declination, sanitary engineering) - 1954 Wilson, J. Greenwood - (travel, public health) - 1950-1953
      - DMPH Finland, 1951-1954 (Box 27, Folder 256)
        Commitments - 1951-1952 Fellowships and Travel Grants - 1951 Forsander, Olof A. - (travel, pediatrics) - 1952-1954
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki College of Nursing, 1952-1955 (Box 27, Folder 257)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki Institute of Industrial Hygiene - Equipment, 1949-1953 (Box 27, Folder 258)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki Institute of Industrial Hygiene - Occupational Health, 1947-1956 (Box 27, Folder 259)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki Institute of Industrial Hygiene - Occupational Health - Documents (12), 1951-1957 (Box 27, Folder 260)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Children's Clinic, 1951-1957 (Box 28, Folder 261)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Department of Bacteriology and Serology - Virus Laboratory, 1946-1957 (Box 28, Folder 262)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Faculty of Medicine, 1946-1958 (Box 28, Folder 263)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Institute of Forensic Medicine, 1947-1955 (Box 28, Folder 264)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Institute of Hygiene, 1951-1957 (Box 28, Folder 265)
      - DMPH Finland - Helsinki University - Psychological Institute, 1952-1955 (Box 28, Folder 266)
      - DMPH Finland, 1947-1956 (Box 28, Folder 267)
        Hultin, Helger - (fellowship, maternal and child health) - 1950-1953 Kaipainen, Wilhelm Johannes - (fellowship, bacteriology) - 1951-1956 Kaprio, Leo A. - (fellowship, public health) - 1947-1955 Karvinen, Esko - (fellowship, physiology) - 1952-1953
      - DMPH Finland, 1947-1954 (Box 28, Folder 268)
        Maki, Helmi - (fellowship, nursing) - 1952-1954 Makkonen, Osmo - (sanitary engineering) - 1947-1954 Miscellaneous - A General Survey of Academic Education in Finland, published by The Finnish Committee on Study and Training in the United States - 1952 Miscellaneous - Donner, K.O. - (zoology) - 1954 Miscellaneous - Paasonen, M.K. - (pharmacology) - 1954 Mustakallio, Eero - (travel, bacteriology and serology) - 1953-1954
      - DMPH Finland, 1951-1957 (Box 28, Folder 269)
        Noro, Leo - (occupational health) - 1952-1953 Nursing - 1951-1955 Pekkarinen, Aimo - (fellowship, pharmacology) - 1952-1953 Pesonen, Niilo - (travel, anatomy) - 1952-1957
      - DMPH Finland, 1946-1954 (Box 29, Folder 270)
        Sanitary Engineering - 1946-1953 Timonen, Kaapo Sakari - (fellowship, anatomy) - 1952-1954
      - DMPH Finland - Turku University - Department of Pharmacology, 1952-1954 (Box 29, Folder 271)
      - DMPH Finland - Turku University - Faculty of Medicine, 1924, 1939, 1947-1955 (Box 29, Folder 272)
      - DMPH Finland - Turku University - Institute of Bacteriology, 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 273)
      - DMPH Finland - Uusima Rural Training Field, 1951-1958 (Box 29, Folder 274)
      - DMPH Finland - Uusima Rural Training Field - Documents (8), 1953-1954 (Box 29, Folder 275)
      - DMPH France - Ancelin, Jacqueline - (fellowships, nursing), 1951-1954 (Box 29, Folder 276)
      - DMPH France, 1947-1954 (Box 29, Folder 277)
        Appell, Genevieve - (clinical psychology) - 1953 Association Culturelle International d'Acueil Universitaire - 1954 Association des Infirmieres Diplomes - 1947-1953
      - DMPH France - Association pour la Sante Mentale de l'Enfance, 1948-1958 (Box 29, Folder 278)
      - DMPH France - Association pour la Sante Mentale de l'Enfance, 1948-1958 (Box 29, Folder 279)
      - DMPH France - Association pour la Sante Mentale de l'Enfance - Documents (21), mostly 1951 (Box 30, Folder 280)
      - DMPH France - Bollack, Claude - (fellowship, experimental surgery), 1953-1956 (Box 30, Folder 281)
      - DMPH France, 1951-1954 (Box 30, Folder 282)
        Bordeaux University - Department of Cardiology - 1953-1954 Centre Antoine Beclere - (medical radiology) - 1954 Centre Psychiatrique de Traitment et Readaptation Sociale - 1951 Coin, Louis - (infantile paralysis) - 1953
      - DMPH France, 1947-1956 (Box 30, Folder 283)
        Comite Americain de Secours Civil - (social work) - 1951-1953 Creusvaux, Genevieve - (fellowship, child guidance) - 1951-1952 David, Myriam Francoise - (fellowship, child psychiatry) - 1947-1956
      - DMPH France - Declinations, 1953-1957 (Box 30, Folder 284)
        Bernhardt, Jean-Philippe - (neurophysiology) - 1953-1957 Centre d'Endocrinologie - Infantile - 1954 Chaudes-Aiques - (hydrotherapy) - 1955 Institute of Psychodidactics - 1954 Kurgansky-Greciskin, M.O. - (respiration) - 1954 Malves, D. - (housing) - 1955 Societe Francaise de Medecine Preventive et Sociale - 1953-1954 Strasbourg Clinique Gynecologique et Obstetricale - 1954
      - DMPH France, 1950-1955 (Box 30, Folder 285)
        Depierre, Germaine F. - (fellowship, pharmacology) - 1950-1953 Dijon University - Faculty of Medicine - 1953 Dinard, Cecile - (child psychiatry) - 1953 Doussaud, Josette - (nursing) - 1951-1953 Fabre, Michel - (medical biology) - 1952 Fessard, Alfred E. - (nerophysiology) - 1952-1955
      - DMPH France - French Red Cross, 1940-1955 (Box 31, Folder 286)
      - DMPH France - French Red Cross - Ecole des Cadres - (nursing), 1948-1955 (Box 31, Folder 287)
      - DMPH France, 1949-1958 (Box 31, Folder 288)
        Hamburger, Jean - (medicine) - 1952 Helmer, France - (public health nursing) - 1954 Hospital Beaujon-Clichy - (laboratory equipment) - 1949-1954 Karli, Pierre - (fellowship, medical biology) - 1953-1958
      - DMPH France - Klein, Marc - (travel, biology), 1945-1954 (Box 31, Folder 289)
      - DMPH France - Lamy, Maurice - (human genetics), 1946-1955 (Box 31, Folder 290)
      - DMPH France - Lefort, Robert - (fellowship, child psychiatry), 1951-1953 (Box 31, Folder 291)
      - DMPH France - Lyon University, 1948-1956 (Box 31, Folder 292)
        Bacteriological Institute - 1951-1956 Department of Biophysics - 1948-1953
      - DMPH France - Lyon University - Faculty of Medicine, 1948-1956 (Box 31, Folder 293)
      - DMPH France - Lyon University - Laboratory of Experimental Surgery, 1948-1959 (Box 31, Folder 294)
      - DMPH France - Lyon University - Physiological Laboratory, 1947-1953 (Box 31, Folder 295)
      - DMPH France - de Mareuil, Amelie Moula - (fellowship, nursing), 1949-1953 (Box 31, Folder 296)
      - DMPH France - Marseille University, 1947-1954 (Box 32, Folder 297)
        Clinique Dermatologique - 1953-1954 Department of Experimental Surgery - 1947-1954
      - DMPH France - Marseille University - Faculty of Medicine, 1947-1955 (Box 32, Folder 298)
      - DMPH France - Marseille University - Hopital de la Conception, 1948-1954 (Box 32, Folder 299)
      - DMPH France - Marseille University - Neurophysiological Laboratory, 1951-1957 (Box 32, Folder 300)
      - DMPH France - Marseille University - Physiological Laboratory, 1948-1957 (Box 32, Folder 301)
      - DMPH France - Metzenthin, Anne Marie - (fellowship, nursing), 1953-1954 (Box 32, Folder 302)
      - DMPH France - Michel, Albert - (fellowship, anesthesiology), 1948-1955 (Box 32, Folder 303)
      - DMPH France, 1945-1954 (Box 32, Folder 304)
        Ministry of Health - 1952-1955 Minkowski, Alexander - (travel pediatrics) - 1951-1957 Miscellaneous - Bargeton, Daniel - (physiology) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Boye, Alfred - (request for treatment) - 1954 Miscellaneous - Cendron, Jean - (pediatrics) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Chataignon, J.M. - (request for assistance in obtaining employment) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Goldenberg, M. - (request for fellowship) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Grupper, Charles - (dermatology) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Lacourbe, Dr. - (Cite Universitaire) - 1955 Miscellaneous - Pigassou-Albouy, R. - (request for equipment) - 1953-1954 Miscellaneous - Rameau, F.A.D. - (request for assistance in setting up laboratory) - 1954 Miscellaneous - Raynaud, Claude - (pediatrics) - 1954 Miscellaneous - Sage, Louis - (request for fellowship) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Sautel, Jacques - (sent literature) - 1954 Miscellaneous - Schapire, Jeannine - (job interview, radiology) - 1952 Miscellaneous - Seneque, Dr. - (anesthesiology, surgery) - 1953 Miscellaneous - Soulairac, A. - (psychophysiology) - 1945-1954
      - DMPH France - Montrouge Ecole Professionelle d'Assistance aux Maldes - (nursing), 1946-1954 (Box 32, Folder 305)
      - DMPH France - Mosinger, Michel - (industrial medicine), 1936-1940, 1945-1957 (Box 33, Folder 306)
      - DMPH France - Nahas, Gabriel Georges - (fellowship, physiology), 1947-1956 (Box 33, Folder 307)
      - DMPH France - Naquet, Robert - (fellowship, neurophysiology), 1952-1956 (Box 33, Folder 308)
      - DMPH France - Oudin, Jacques - (immunology), 1949-1955 (Box 33, Folder 309)
      - DMPH France, 1947-1955 (Box 33, Folder 310)
        Paris University - Clinique Baudelocques - (pediatrics) - 1947-1955 Documents (17) - 1950-1953
      - DMPH France, 1947-1955 (Box 33, Folder 311)
      - DMPH France, 1946-1954 (Box 33, Folder 312)
        Paris University - Ecole De Puericulture - (pediatrics) - 1946-1953 Paris University - Faculty of Medicine - 1948-1954
      - DMPH France - Paris University - Hopital des Enfants Malades, 1935, 1945-1959 (Box 33, Folder 313)
      - DMPH France - Paris University - Hospice de la Salpetriere - Laboratory of Neurophysiology, 1946-1955 (Box 33, Folder 314)
      - DMPH France - Paris University - Laboratory of General Physiology, 1946-1953 (Box 33, Folder 315)
      - DMPH France - Pasteur Institute, 1947-1950, 1955-1956 (Box 33, Folder 316)
      - DMPH France - Pasteur Institute - Virus research, 1951-1954 (Box 34, Folder 317)
      - DMPH France, 1951-1956 (Box 34, Folder 318)
        Pichaut, Janine - (nursing) - 1951-1953 Quievreuse, Genevieve - (fellowship, nursing) - 1954-1955 Sanitary Engineering - 1952-1953 Sevres Centre International de Pedagogie - (nursing) - 1952-1956
      - DMPH France, 1953-1959 (Box 34, Folder 319)
        Soissons Health Center - 1955-1959 Documents - 22 items - see box 35 - 1953-1959
      - DMPH France - Strasbourg School of Nurses and Social Workers, 1945-1954 (Box 34, Folder 320)
      - DMPH France - Strasbourg University, 1948-1958 (Box 34, Folder 321)
        Center For Surgical Research - Laboratory Raymond Poincare - 1951-1953 Faculty of Medicine - 1951-1954 Institute of Physiology - 1948-1958
      - DMPH France - Strasbourg University - Laboratory of Applied Physiology, 1951-1954 (Box 34, Folder 322)
      - DMPH France - Strasbourg University - Laboratory of Applied Physiology - Reports (2), 1956-1957 (Box 34, Folder 323)
      - DMPH France - Toulouse University, 1951-1958 (Box 34, Folder 324)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1951-1955 Laboratory of Physiology - 1951-1958
      - DMPH France - Soissons Health Center - Documents (22 items), 1953-1959 (Box 35, Folder 325)
      - DMPH France, 1949-1956 (Box 36, Folder 326)
        Toumanoff, Constantin - (malariology) - 1949-1955 Vacherot, Marie - (nursing) - 1953-1954 Vanier, Colette - (nursing) - 1951-1952 Vieuchange, Jean - (travel, uirology) - 1953-1956
      - DMPH France - Viborel, Lucien - (public health), 1945-1957 (Box 36, Folder 327)
      - DMPH France - Viborel, Lucien - (public health) - Reports (2), 1946-1949 (Box 36, Folder 328)
      - DMPH France, 1950-1954 (Box 36, Folder 329)
        Vigne, Jacques - (medical physics) - 1953 Witz, Jean and Witz-Berger, Mrs. - (fellowship, surgery) - 1950-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Bartels, Heinz - (fellowship, physiology), 1949-1954 (Box 36, Folder 330)
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1955 (Box 36, Folder 331)
        Bavarian Biological Experimental Station - 1949-1954 Beutelspacher, Irmgard - (nursing) - 1954-1955 Bondy, Curt - (psychology) - 1948-1952
      - DMPH Germany - Born University, 1948-1957 (Box 36, Folder 332)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1948-1954 Institute of Anatomy - 1952-1957
      - DMPH Germany - Bremer Institute for Advanced Study in Health and Human Relations, 1951-1952 (Box 36, Folder 333)
      - DMPH Germany - Cologne University, 1950-1955 (Box 36, Folder 334)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1952-1955 Institute of Physiology - (Schneider, Max) - 1950-1955
      - DMPH Germany - Declinations, 1951-1955 (Box 36, Folder 335)
        Borelli, S. - (dermatology) - 1953-1954 Freund, Hugo - (international health problems) - 1953-1954 Gelinsky, Hans - (physiology) - 1954 Gilman, Helmut - (cardiology) - 1954-1955 Heinz, Karl - (opthalmology) - 1953 Hufschmidt, Hans J. - (neurophysiology) - 1951-1952 Kontzey, Erno - (Hungarian Medical Assocation) - 1952-1953 Meyer-Delvendal, W. - (cancer research) - 1954 Munich Institute for Infectious and Tropical Diseases - 1954 Schniessle, Walter - (surgery) - 1954 Sokol, Kurt - (gynaecology) - 1953-1954 Stender, Arist - (neurosurgery) - 1955 Tremblau, E.H. - (psychiatry) - 1952-1953
      - DMPH Germany, 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 336)
        Derbolowsky, Udo - (fellowship applicant, psychiatry) - 1952-1954 Dieterich, Bernd - (fellowship, sanitary engineering) - 1951-1953
      - DMPH Germany, 1950-1957 (Box 37, Folder 337)
        Dodt, Eberhard - (fellowship, physiology) - 1953-1957 Dorpinghaus, Gertrud - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1954
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1955 (Box 37, Folder 338)
        Dusseldorf Academy of Public Health - 1948-1954 Dusseldorf University - Faculty of Medicine - 1948-1955
      - DMPH Germany - Effenberger, Ernst - (fellowship, industrial hygiene), 1954-1955 (Box 37, Folder 339)
      - DMPH Germany - Frankfurt University, 1948-1954 (Box 37, Folder 340)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1951-1953 Institute for Vegetative Physiology - 1948-1954 School of Public Health - 1950-1952
      - DMPH Germany - Freiburg University, 1946-1954 (Box 37, Folder 341)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1951-1954 Neurophysiological Clinic - 1946-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Geibel, Lieselotte - (fellowship, nursing), 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 342)
      - DMPH Germany, 1950-1955 (Box 37, Folder 343)
        General Correspondence - Morison, Robert S. - 10/13/55 General Correspondence - Redeker, Franz - 1950-1952 General Correspondence - Unitarian Service Committee - 1955 German Health Officers' Visit to United States - 1951-1953
      - DMPH Germany - Gottingen University, 1948-1954 (Box 37, Folder 344)
        Faculty of Medicine - 1952-1954 Institute of Physiology - 1948-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Grauhan, Antje - (fellowship, nursing), 1953-1954 (Box 38, Folder 345)
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1958 (Box 38, Folder 346)
        Hamburg Institute of Hygiene - 1948-1958 Documents (4) - 1954-1957
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1958 (Box 38, Folder 347)
      - DMPH Germany, 1949-1954 (Box 38, Folder 348)
        Hamburg Institute for Tropical Medicine - 1950-1954 Hamburg University - Neurological Clinic - 1949-1953
      - DMPH Germany - Aannapel, Carola - (travel, psychiatry), 1951-1954 (Box 38, Folder 349)
      - DMPH Germany, 1951-1955 (Box 38, Folder 350)
        Hamperl, Herwig - (travel, pathology) - 1953-1955 Harmsden, Hans - (travel, public health) - 1951-1953
      - DMPH Germany - Heidelberg School of Nursing, 1955-1958 (Box 38, Folder 351)
      - DMPH Germany - Heidelberg University - Faculty of Medicine, 1952-1954 (Box 38, Folder 352)
      - DMPH Germany - Heidelberg University - Institute of Psychosomatic Medicine, 1950-1956 (Box 38, Folder 353)
      - DMPH Germany - Heidelberg University - Physiological Institute, 1950-1956 (Box 38, Folder 354)
      - DMPH Germany, 1952-1957 (Box 38, Folder 355)
        Henaton, Hans D. - (fellowship, neurophysiology) - 1953-1957 Hennessen, Walter A. - (fellowship declination, virology) - 1952
      - DMPH Germany, 1951-1957 (Box 39, Folder 356)
        Hild, Walther - (fellowship, neurology) - 1951-1954 Hubener, Hans Joachim - (fellowship, physiology) - 1952-1957
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1954 (Box 39, Folder 357)
        Jores, Arthur - (psychosomatic medicine) - 1948-1953 Karlsruhe Technical High School - (publications) - 1950-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Kehl, Robert - (fellowship, internal medicine), 1953-1956 (Box 39, Folder 358)
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1953 (Box 39, Folder 359)
        Kiel Children's Hospital - 1948-1952 Kiel University - Department of Anatomy Kiel University - Physiological Institute - 1948-1953
      - DMPH Germany, 1949-1954 (Box 39, Folder 360)
        Knoche, Hermann - (anatomy) - 1952-1954 Klone, William - (fellowship, nursing) - 1951-1954 Kroeber, Ursula - (fellowship, nursing) - 1951-1954 Kuhnau, Joachim - (travel, biochemistry) - 1949-1953
      - DMPH Germany, 1950-1958 (Box 39, Folder 361)
        Lagarie, Gerd W. - (fellowship, public health) - 1951-1953 Ludwig, Friedrich Karl - (fellowship, pathology) - 1952-1958 Mannheim Child Guidance Clinic - 1950-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Marburg University - Faculty of Medicine, 1950-1956 (Box 39, Folder 362)
      - DMPH Germany - Medical Education, 1947-1955 (Box 39, Folder 363)
      - DMPH Germany, 1949-1955 (Box 39, Folder 364)
        Merten, Richard - (medicine) - 1949-1953 Meyer-Miekeleit, Rudolf W. - (fellowship, neurophysiology) - 1951-1954 Mielke, Fred - (fellowship, psychiatry) - 1953-1955
      - DMPH Germany - Miscellaneous, 1945-1955 (Box 40, Folder 365)
        Grants for Working Germany - 5/9/45 - 12/31/54 (list) Abendroth, Hilmar - (internal medicine) - 1953 Andrejewsky, C. - (request for Fellowship) - 1954 Brengelmann, J.C. - (psychology) - 1950-1952 Eibl-Eibersfeldt, Irenaus - (psychobiology) - 1954 Gravenstein, Joachim - (anesthesiology) - 1951 Griesser, Gerd - (thoracic surgery) - 1952 Hase, Brigitte - (pediatrics) - 1951-1952 Holscher, Dr. - (invitation to 100th anniversary celebration of the birth of Paul Erlich and Emil von Behring) - 1953 Hohman, G. - (opthalmology) - 1952 Hoof, Doris - (opthalmology) - 1948-1953 Koch, Ilse - (cardiology) - 1953 Kodlin, D. - (physiology) - 1953 Manen-John, Lucie - (physiology) - 1952-1953 Marchichini, Alfred - (dermatology) - 1953 Moser, Max - "Todays Situation in the Attitudes and Activities of German Youth in the field of Citizenship" - 1951 Niedergerke, Rolf - (physiology) - 1952 Poeck, Klaus K. - (neurology) - 1953 Rapalski, Adam - (preventive medicine) - 1955 Roemer, G.A. - (psychiatry) - 1953 Roka, Ladislau - (chemical physiology) - 1954 Schleussing, Hans G. - (psychiatry) - 1954-1955 Schneider, Dietrich - (neurophysiology) - 1952 Schoenbach, Gerhard - (cardiology) - 1953 Stroeder, J. - (pediatrics) - 1952-1953 Unna, Klaus - (pharmacology) - 1948 Wellman, George - (veterinary medicine) - 1951 Zutt, Jurt - (psychiatry) - 1951-1952
      - DMPH Germany - Mand, Rudolf - (travel, physiology), 1948-1953 (Box 40, Folder 366)
      - DMPH Germany - Munich University, 1950-1955 (Box 40, Folder 367)
        Child Guidance Center - 1950-1952 Faculty of Medicine - 1951-1955 Pharmacological Institute - 1950-1954
      - DMPH Germany, 1948-1953 (Box 40, Folder 368)
        Nursing - 1948-1953 Eventual Candidates - 1949-1950
      - DMPH Germany, 1952-1955 (Box 40, Folder 369)
        Ochwalt, Bruno - (fellowship, physiology) - 1952-1955 Opitz, Hanz - (travel, nursing) - 1953-1954 Pankow, Gisela - (declination, endocrinology) - 1952-1953
      - DMPH Germany, 1947-1954 (Box 40, Folder 370)
        Rothmund, Hildegard - (travel, public health) - 1952-1954 Rummel, Walter - (pharmacology) - 1953 Sanitary Engineering - 1947-1954
      - DMPH Germany, 1934-1954 (Box 40, Folder 371)
        Schoen, Rudolf - (travel, medicine) - 1949-1953 Schrier, Kurt - (declination, biochemistry) - 1948-1953 Schriever, Hans - (physiology) - 1934, 1953 Schroeder, Wilhelm - (fellowship, physiology) - 1948-1954
      - DMPH Germany - Stuttgart Technical High School - (sanitary engineering), 1949-1951 (Box 40, Folder 372)
      - DMPH Germany - Stuttgart Technical High School, 1952-1956 (Box 41, Folder 373)